Visit turkision.com for more!
Mother!
-Enough! Pull yourself together!
-Mother!
Mehmed Bey stop right there!
Let go!
Enough! My father is dying!
Stop it already! Alaeddin...
...do something come on!
Let me go!
Stop it already!
Gonca.
This hasn’t ended.
This hasn’t ended like this.
Father, father Pull yourself together.
Father open your eyes please!
-Father!
-Let go!
-Let go of me!
-Hold his head.
Come on Yakup Bey!
Come on, pull yourself!
Come on father, please.
-Father, please.
-I will kill you Alaeddini
Open your eyes, come on.
-Come on father please.
-Come on.
Father please, open your eyes.
-Come here!
-Attack!
Alps!
Stop, stop, stop.
My Bey.
After the spy lady slipped out of our fingers..
..we heard the swords clashing.
We came here.
Those attackers are Mongols.
They disguised themselves as Kayi.
Dastards.
What could be the reason behind this, my Bey?
Why would they commit such trickery?
Those who attacked Yakup Bey in
Yenisehir were also disguised as alps.
It seems they want to drive a
wedge between Kayi and Germiyanids.
They want war.
Father, father;
Father please open your eyes!
-Yakup, my Bey.
-Father please open your eyes!
Father please come to your senses!
Father open your eyes please!
-Yakup Bey.
-Father please!
Father!
I will kill you sooner or later, Alaeddin!
I will kill you!
Who are you killing in whose palace, Mehmed?
-Take him to prison.
-I won't go!
-I won't go anywhere!
-Father!
-Father open your eyes!
-Alaeddin say something!
Father; Open youfeyes please!
-Father!
-You neither have palace or’land anymore.
All of you are done fori
I can't hear his heartbeats’
Shut your mouths, enough!
Alaeddin.
He is choking on his tongue!
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Father please don't leave us.
Alaeddin, please say something;
Tell me, is he going to live?
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
O Healer!
-Father! Father?
-Ya Allah!
-Father!
-O Healer!
-Allah!
-Father!
O Healer!
Father!
Gorklu Khan has died, my Bey.
Who is after this mess?
Tajeddin Noya
Look here.
Who is this lady, my Bey?
She is not a stranger, Bayindir Bey.
Before Tajeddin Noyan attacked with his armies..
..he wants to weaken Kayis
with his assassins, Osman Bey.
How do you know of this, Elcim Hatun?
I heard it while escaping from them.
That is the reason why they
disguise themselves as alps.
When I was a captive, I escaped by wearing one.
Now it all makes sense.
Osman Bey. I won't leave my family in his hands.
-Orhan, -My Bey.
You will go to take Gunduz Bey..
..and his brother's wife with Elcim Hatun.
As you command, my Bey.
-Boran. Konur, Turahan.
-My Bey
You will come with me.
The rest of the alps will go with Orhan.
We are heading to Yenisehir.
If something happens to Yakup Bey..
..then disorder will take place.
We won't be able to prevent it.
Come on alps!
-Ya Allah!
-Please open your eyes!
Ya Allah!
Mehmed stop!
-Mehmed!
-Brother, stop!
I will take your life Alaeddin.
-I will kill you! My father is dead!
-Mehmed, pull yourself together!
-What are you doing?
-Stop, Mehmed!
I will take your life!
Let go!
Stop!
Father!
-Father? Father!
-Your father is alive!
Your father is alive, Mehmed!
Your father is alive!
Let go of me Mehmed!
-Alaeddin Bey!
His breath is slow.
-Father!
Mehmed, get Yakup Bey up!
-Get him up!
-Come on fatheri
Make way.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
O Healer! Ya Allah!
Heal him, my Creator.
Heal him, my Allah!
Father.
-Put him down slowly.
-Slowly.
Alaeddin Bey, say something. Is he alive?
He is alright, for now.
However, we need to be cautious.
We need to leave him alone.
As you saw, Alaeddin save Yakup Bey’s life.
Saadet Hatun, Mehmed Bey..
..will you behave?
You tricked me, saying it was duty.
What kind of duty is this, living in this house?
What if that Tall Shahzade..
..abducts Gonca Hatun while I was here?
-I will abduct Gonca Hatun!
-Stop!
Look here, you never had
a serious beating from me.
If you step outside..
..I will hang your to ceiling from your feet
Go, sit here!
Enough of this.
My Cerkutay.
Are you alright?
Are you in pain?
I am alright, my hatun.
It is alright.
Father, who did this to you?
No one can do anything to me!
My valiant.
Tell me who did this, and I will punish them!
No one can touch my father!
Praise be!
Your father can take a
hundred more beating, just to..
..look at your face without shame tomorrow.
Ghazi.
Remember, when I told you about a duty?
Now it is time for duty.
I will go, Ghazi.
No, never!
I just got you! Where will you go?
No, never, never.
Son, Ghazi.
Ghazi.
For the state.
For duty.
We will be seperated for a time.
We will do a secret work with you.
No one will know about this.
That secret, belongs to you now.
That secret, belongs to you now
That is your first duty, Ghazi Alp.
Keep your head up.
This duty is very important.
Only you..
..me..
..your mother..
..and Osman Bey know of this.
Did you say Osman Bey?
-Did Osman Bey give me this duty?
-Yes.
This first duty, is quite hard, Cerkutay Bey.
However, if it is for the state..
..it is a command!
My Cerkutay.
We always miss each other.
That burden is upon you.
However, I promise..
..after we get through this duty..
..then we won't get seperated again.
-Do you promise?
I promise.
A father's..
..and a Cerkutay promise.
Where is the dastard who shot my father, Osman Be
-Easy!
Mehmed Bey, easy!
Mehmed.
Stop.
Listen to your father.
So you will have a long life.
Everybody out.
I will talk to Yakup Bey privately.
Firstly...
...with Allah's blessing...
...and then thanks to your
Alaaddin, I'm alive, Osman Bey.
Tell me.
Who attempted to kill me?
Tajeddin Noyan.
Tajeddin Noya
What wduld he do with us?
Great Olcaytu’s nephew...
What would he gain by killing me?
Yakup Bey.
They know you are using your children as spies.
They know your weak spot.
Tell me.
If you died here,
...who would your house blame?
You and I would turn against each other.
Beys would gather behind us.
They want to make Turks kill each other.
But thanks to Allah,
...we didn’t let that happen.
We didn’t let them achieve.
Thanks to Allah.
-Thanks to Allah.
-They are uncomfortable with our success...
...and what we will do next.
Yet, Yakup Bey, you got
overwhelmed by your ambition...
...and stood in my way.
You're right, Osman Bey.
You’re right.
Especially after I heard...
...what my hatun and children did..
I didn't know.
But it doesn't matter anymore.
You once told me "A person who
can't make his family listen to him...
...can’t be a bey for his people.”
If Allah permits, I will make up for...
...what I said and what we did.
When I recover...
...we will walk together on this path.
Why are you smiling, Osman Bey?
Tell me.
Can you risk your life for me when it's time?
When it's time,
...can you send your alps to death?
When we get much more powerful,
...can you hinder your arrogance?
Tell me.
Well...
Just as I guessed.
That’s what I thought.
Yakup Bey.
We can't walk together on this path.
Stand neither against me nor behind me.
For now,
...just get out of my way.
Pity! Look at yourself.
Ito# ma ho you are crying for is our enemy!
Orhan and his family only aim to destroyed us!
Love? Passion?
Not real!
Open your eyes!
Not real?
You won't let him deceive you anymore.
You won’t even mention Orhan's name again!
You hear me?
Did you hear me?
Soldier!
Send a message to Lords.
Gorklu Khan's death ruined everything.
We need to gather and make a new plan.
I expect to see all the Lords in my castle.
On every hill looking down on their cave,
...there are good nokers.
They must have blocked the valley completely.
In case of an attack, they let
each other know with red arrows.
It'll be very hard to get inside.
Dogs.
They're laying traps all around.
My Shahzade.
Their cave is well protected.
Yes.
First,
...we need to kill the archers on the hills.
We are just a few.
If they manage to send a message,
...we will fail.
Orhan Bey is right.
Before they die,
..they will shoot the red arrows.
Well... So..
How will we get inside?
My Shahzade, we can attack through the valley.
We can hit them from their back.
We’ll arrive there in time
and save Elcim Hatun’s family.
Those dogs only speak this language.
-We should attack.
-No.
They will kill your family instantly.
-Aykurt.
-My Shahzade.
Tell the bey of the tribe...
...to give me his best ten alps.
Being too many is useless.
Orhan Bey.
What’s your plan?
How will we get in their cave?
By using our most effective weapon.
We’ll leave at dawn. Come on!
As you order, my Shahzadej
Let me help you, father.
I don't want!
I don’t want.
I don’t want anything from you anymore.
Yakup Bey.
I did this to...
Don’t you even speak.
Mehmed is young...
...and inexperienced.
He made a mistake.
But you
Who are you...
...to try to make my daughter a spy
I'm her mother.
And your hatun, Yakup Bey.
I did this because I cared about our future.
-By using my daughter?
-Yakup Bey.
Say no more.
You made me..
...get my head down, Saadet.
Now go...
...and apologize to the hatuns.
What?
You can ask me to do anything.
But not this.
If you want me to forgive you,
...you’ll first ask forgiveness...
...for what you did.
Easy, father.
And you?
How could you...
..do this to me and yourself?
Didn't you think about it at all?
I had nothing else to do, father.
My mother put me in such a tight spot...
When...
...a man loves someone.
...he wants to trust, Gonca.
Today...
...I lost my trust in your mother.
My heart is burning.
Beside this suffering,
...I don't feel this arrow's pain at all.
It's you who started the fire, father.
Now you're blaming my mother, but...
...it was you who first
sent my mother after Kayi.
You are guilty as much as...
....my mother and brother are.
Lords are in our hands now.
Call the Beys now.
Yes my Bey.
Can I tell you something, Bala Hatun?
Saadet Hatun wants to see you.
Aameen.
Let her come, Kismet.
Yes, Saadet Hatun.
I am listening to you.
Yakup Bey regained his health, thanks to Allah.
Thanks to Allah.
Thanks to you...
Thanks to Alaeddin Bey.
I came here to thank you.
We did our duty, Saadet Hatun.
They say ’’everyone does what suits them”.
I am expecting you to understand me, Bala.
When I saw my Bey...
...on his deathbed...
..I lost my mind.
I am sorry.
Did you just...
...lose your mind, Saadet Hatun?
How can someone turn her own daughter into a spy?
What kind of a mother are you?
I did not mean to hearm you.
It was misunderstood.
One cannot play with love, Bala.
They fell in love before...
...I gave her the duty.
You..
...you dirtied the love of those two children.
What is done is done.
I am paying the price of what I did.
And may you..
...give me your blessings in doomsday.
I will not shake that hand, Saadet.
If I really...
...believe that you regret one day...
..then I can shake your hand.
Think well...
..before you do something now.
You won't change, Saadet.
The love you have for power overtook you.
May Allah help you.
Our spies sent us a letter.
Olivia Hatun invited Lords to Atranos.
We got rid of the Gorklu Khan issue.
They will take their heads
out of their hiding holes.
They must be after a treacherous move, my Bey.
That is right. Yakup Bey was shot.
Gorklu Khan died.
Now... they will look for
an opportunity to revolt.
-But we won't let them.
-What are we going to do then, my Bey?
We will speak their language.
Konur! Tell our Alps to get ready.
You will surround Atranos when Lords gather.
Yes my Bey.
And we will take the Lord of Kite.
Did you do what my father said, mother?
Yakup
If it wasn't for you, I would destroy this palace!
What happened, mother?
That Bala disgraced me!
Disgraced me!
She did not shake my hand!
She made me beg like a dog, Mehmet!
Ah... Ah, my father, ahh!
My father is making a mistake, mother! A mistake!
Will we forgive them
because they saved our lives?
Order me... Order me...
...to burn this palace!
We won't do that, Mehmet.
We will core it.
We will core it in such a way that...
...this palace will collapse on them.
They disgraced your father, your
sister and your family before everyone!
They will pay for this.
-We will not stop, Mehmet!
-As you say, mother.
They were our rivals until now.
But after what happened..
We have our enemies, Mehmet.
Until now..
..I wanted to hurt their feelings.
But now... I will cut their hearts into pieces.
We will, my mother! We will!
But... don't do something in front of others...
...and make your father angry with you.
We will do it secretly.
We will, mother. We will, don't worry.
Stop!
Stop, where are you going?
Where are you going?
Come.
Where?
Come..
Where are you going?
The Righteous!
Malhun!
-Osman!
-Don’t be afraid..
My Osman...
Did you have the same dream again?
It was... It was the same.
But...
...you know, I told you that there was a Hatun.
I told you that she was walking towards
a tree but that I couldn't see her face.
Right, you couldn't...
I saw her.
This time, I saw her face.
It was met
I saw myself...
...wearing an ihram.
Malhun...
Look...
I know very well what is in your mind...
...and what is in your heart.
Osman.
What I saw was the way of pilgrimage.
But... right before I woke up...
...the horsemen were coming at me again.
I drew my bow and was
about to shoot it when it broke.
Was this a sign?
Is it better to go or to stay?
I am confused.
Now... as you know...
...things are harder now.
We are between two fires.
In the palace, in Yenisehir...
...before the folk, of course...
...of course, your presence here gives me power.
Of course you give me power.
But this dream you had..
...going to Hajj...
Is it better for you to stay or to go?
You have to make that decision.
Look... No matter what happens...
No matter what you decide...
...I will accept it.
I am with you.
May my Allah keep you with us.
Elcim Hatun!
How did Tajeddin Noyan start attacking you?
He asked for an army from
my father for the Mongol war.
And my father rejected him.
When he understood that he was
not going to let us live in peace...
...and that he was going to shed blood...
...we migrated from our lands.
Butthat Tajeddin Noyan..
...is such a bad and revengeful man that...
..he came after us.
He wanted to take his revenge
because we rejected him.
He martyred my mother and my brother.
And he captured us.
Elcim Hatun..
Do you know something important...
...about Tajeddin Noyan’s army?
The assassins I told Osman Bey about.
There is one among them that..
...is the most cruel.
That person was a student of those
who followed the path of Hasan Sabbah.
Maybe that cruel person was
the one who shot Yakup Bey.
Elcim Hatun.
Can we find that cruel person?
No one saw that person
or hear that person's voice.
They say that person takes lives like a shadow...
...and then disappears.
Like a shadow, huh?
We know how to drown that shadow in our light.
We will send them all away
from this land, Elcim Hatun.
All.
Orhan Bey...
Thank you.
For everything.
You are risking your lives
for my father and my aunt.
But you should know...
We do not forget the good...
...or the bad done to us.
We will pay you back for this.
Thank you Elcim Hatun.
But don't worry...
We will take your revenge today...
...and with Allah’s consent, we
will take your father and your aunt.
Come on.
Alaeddin... -How?
Did you have a good time?
What do you mean?
My heart ached every time I saw you.
My conscience took control of my heart, Alaeddin.
I didn’t do any of this on purpose.
-I had to.
-What did you have to do?
What did you have to do?
So that you want to talk, let’s talk.
What did you think? Did
you say ”1 can fool Alaeddin"?
Look, Gonca. I've been thinking
about this since I heard about it.
I've been thinking about
the things we did together.
Which one was real?
Which one was the game?
Tell me; Was your love a game?
Did you play a game when
you risked your life for my life?
If all that was a game..
..how can you still look into my eyes like this?
None of them; I swear, none
of them was a game, Alaeddint
You can say anything to me,
you can do anything to me...
But you cannot put me and
my mother in the same pot.
For me...
...the only thing that is true is you.
My love for you... -No.
Do not expect me to believe you now.
I've rebuilt all the walls..
...that I broke for you, Trickster.
Gonca Hatun.
I won't let my heart speak anymore.
It’s over.
I know.
But don't make it end like this, Alaaddin.
Just listen to me.
Then I'll go, anyway.
You listened to your mother and
betrayed me| You became a spy, Goncai
I didn’t! Alaaddin, I didn’t!
Once! I swear...
...I had to do it only once!
You always say duties matter most.
And you keep silent.
Please see this as a duty!
Your duty was me; It was me!
Your duty was me!
It was me.
I accepted you as my dearest!
I protected you from everything.
You made your thorns bleed me!
I will spit blood forever, Gonca Hatun!
Don't talk like this, Alaaddin.
You said it’d be hard but we'd
overcome hardships together.
I believed in you and us.
You know what?
I was so scared before.
But I thought our love could
overcome any hardships.
I thought you would believe me.
And then what happened?
It's you who falls down
against the first hardship!
I would face any hardships with you.
Any hardships.
But you betrayed me.
I didn’t.
You betrayed us, Gonca.
Now I have a duty.
Get out of my way.
I don't need to keep it anymore.
You ruined everything!
Everything! Everything!
Barbarians!
Princess Maria.
They can do anything to be allies, huh?
Then we can’t give the princess
to Mongolians or Byzantine.
-There shouldn't be an alliance.
-There won't be.
-There shouldn’t be an alliance
-There won’t be.
There won't be, Bala.
But there is something wrong with the princess.
You need to fin’d out what it is.
You need to find out what it is.
You must be hungry.
We’ve brought you food.
Kismet Hatun.
You've been our guest for long, but...
...we didn't meet before.
I'm Bala Hatun, Osman Bey's wife.
A guest?
Do you always treat your guests like this?
You’ve been dragging me around for days!
We're doing this for your good, princess.
We got rid of a man like Gorklu Khan thanks to us.
My good?
You ruined everything!
All my plans failed!
I was going to marry Gorklu Khan.
You keep calling us barbarians.
The real barbarian was Gorklu Khan.
Don't tell me..
...you'd marry such a man with your own will.
I won’t believe that, princess.
I was going to have this marriage
for Great Byzantine Empire.
You can't understand me.
Great Byzantine, huh?
What you call Great Byzantine...
...send you around like an item, princess.
Open your ears and hear me well.
Gorklu Khan is dead.
Now they want to make you marry Tajeddin Noyan.
Tajeddin Noyan?
They keep changing the man you'll marry...
...without asking you and taking your consent.
How could you accept this?
But it's not what we agreed.
No, it can't be.
Princess.
You have a different issue.
You can trust me.
Can you please leave me alone?
My Bey, Lord is coming.
Come on
Lord!
-We were waiting for you!
-What for?
You have an account to give us!
Alps, attack!
Come on
Still no news from Lord Leon?
We know they're marching to Atranos.
-What's going on, soldier?
-My Lord.
Osman's commander Konur..
...besieged Atranos with his alps.
Tell soldiers to take battle formation.
Reinforce the gates! I want archers
on the walls and in the inner castle.
Come on!
Feel at ease, my friends.
AtranoS walls are impassable.
Although the walls are impassable,
...Osman will find a way
in if he wants to get inside.
Close the doors of the secret passage.
Soldiers, do what she said.
Well thought, Olivia.
Osman will try those tunnels like a rat.
He wouldn't come though
the gate of Great Atranos.
Lord.
You're out of breath, Lord.
But we aren't barbarians as you think.
We need you.
Yagiz Alp. Kirbag.
Take this.
You must be thirsty.
Drink it. Drink it.
Why are you not killing me, Osman Bey?
How do you know I didn't kill you?
The water you just drank is poisonous.
You... What have you done?
How could you do this?
Bring him.
Mongol Captive Camp
They are not like Mongolians.
Samil.
In the Mongolian army,
...there are various tribes...
...who scattered away from the llkhanid State.
You heard Elcim Hatun.
There are also Hasan Sabbah's
followers among them now.
Our job has always been hard.
But it's much harder now.
Orhan Bey.
You think this plan will work?
What if it doesn’t, Elcim Hatun?
We will just lose our lives, right?
-Yes, but...
-If you are afraid,
...stay back.
we grew up with the smell of the
blood Mongolians shed, Orhan Bey.
Not in palaces.
We can hold on.
Then, play well.
Come on.
-Everyone to positions!
-Was Nicea and Prusa informed?
Alps can not exit, my Lord.
The castle is completely surrounded.
Turks are coming!
Just a couple of horsemen;
Is it Osman?
Tell your Lords, Osman Bey has arrived!
Open the doors!
What a confidence Osman hast
-He must have something.
-The Lord of Kite is in our hands!
Now, either open the doors..
..or we will destroy them!
Come.
Here!
I brought the Lord! Open the gates!
Open the gates!
Never!
I will never allow him inside my castle!
He has Lord Leon.
Let him in. He can not do anything by himself.
We have the upper hand here.
He has the Lord of Kite.
Let him in.
Soldiers!
Open the gates!
Have you never heard what happens..
..to those who do wrong to us?
Here.
Now.
He will tell you how he sold you out..
..how he betrayed you!
However, you will not like it.
Come on.
Nokers!
We are not enemy.
We brought the captive you couldn't catch.
Aren't you looking for this girl?
We are, but who are you?
Father?
Elcim Hatun.
Don’t expose yourself.
Come on, get ahold of yourself.
We are the alps Tajeddin
Noyan gathered from frontiers!
If you strike us..
..he will not let any of you live.
Now..
Tajeddin Noyan promised
us gold in return of this captive.
Now give us our gold.
We will give you your gold.
However, give us the girl first.
Stop there.
The only thing we will give you..
..is the cold steel of our swords.
Alps!
Elcim Hatuni
Now..
Tell them everything.
Why would a person who knows he will die..
..tell everything?
You will tell..
..if you need to tell..
..to live.
Here.
Do you know what is inside bf this?
This has your cure in it.
The antidote.
Osman Bey!
-Stop there.
-Osman Bey, the antidote!
Stop there, stop!
Now..
You will tell them everything.
Emir Gorklu Khan sent me a messenger.
To serve him.
Phelped him against Osman Bey.
Osman Bey, give the antidote!
Osman Bey!
Osman Bey! The antidote!
Tell them how you betrayed your friends.
I cannot say more.
You wanted this.
Osman Bey, alright!
Alright.
Emir Gorklu Khan..
He was going to take every castle of Lords.
And you sided with him knowing that?
Osman Bey, give me the antidote!
It is not over!
Tell them.
Gorklu Khan, after taking the castles..
..he was going to give them all
to me, that's why I helped him.
Osman Bey, there is not much time!
I will die! Give me that antidote!
Osman Bey!
Get off!
So you want the antidote.
..you want this.
What did you do?
This was my last chance to live!
Lord.
The thing you drank, was only water.
There was no poison in it.
The thing that circles your blood..
..is only fear of death.
Father.
We were late, Orhan Bey.
We were late.
Elcim Hatun.
He is not my father.
What?
He is not my father, Orhan Bey.
My Allah.
My Allah, thank you.
Orhan...
No one will take you from me today!
Karacelasun.
Now I will take your life!
This time..
..this time you won’t get away!
First, tell me.
Where is Gunduz Bey?
Nokersi
Leave none of them alivet
-Alps!
-Ya Allah!
I am leaving this dog to you.
I won’t kill this dog.
So you sold your long friends to Mongols.
A noble Lord of..
..Roman Empire is..
..being humiliated in front of you.
You don't even move;
You should've thought about
that before selling Rome out.
Was I the only one?
Do you think..
.. I am the only one?
What do you want from us, Osman Bey?
The tax you promised to pay.
Right now.
Osman Bey... We cannot pay you in a week!
Today!
You will pay it today!
Or else..
I will take your properties...
...as a cost.
And this is my last warning.
There is no other way, Lords!
I will send a letter to the Emperor.
What are you going to say, Olivia?
I will ask him to send..
...the Executioner of Roman Empire with his men.
If the Executioner of Roman Empire comes...
...not only Osman...
...but everyone living on this land
will suffer more than they ever did.
We cannot stop the Executioner
of Roman Empire, Olivia!
I know.
I know that even the Emperor
cannot make him listen.
I did not forget what he did.
But we have no other choice!
Roman Empire was founded on these sacrifices.
And it will live forever with those sacrifices.
Only the Executioner of Roman
Empire can defeat Osman.
If he comes...
...Orhan...
They will all die.
Stand up!
You will pay the price of...
...what you did to my family and my people!
Stop...
Stand up!
You dog... Today...
...I told you that you wouldn't
be able to escape from me.
Now, Karacelasun..
...you will either speak here...
..or I will cut your head off!
Speak, you dastard; Where is my father?
-Where is my aunt? Speak!
-Stop, Elcim Hatun!
Speak!
Do you think you can find them?
Tajeddin Noyan..
...prepared such a death for them that...
-Tell me!
-Elcim Hatun!
Tell me, or I will rip your heart out!
Hatun... I told you to stop.
Calm down.
My Shahzade. I know how to make this dog speak.
Allow me to make him speak.
We will make this dog speak!
But not here..
We will make him speak in Yenisehir.
Bayindir Bey! Take this dastard dog to Yenisehir.
He will wait in the dungeon.
Don't worry about that, my Shahzade.
He will not die..
...before he says something important.
Elcim Hatun..
We will learn where your father...
...and aunt are from this dog.
We will make him speak.
But first, we will go to Yenisehir.
Alps!
Take our martyrs down from there.
Come on.
My Allah, may You give relief to my heart.
Let's have some rest here.
May you be safe from evil,
and mercy of Allah be upon you.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
May Allah accept it.
We didn't see you here.
-I hope we are not disturbing you.
-Not at all.
Here.
Thank you.
I saw you when you came to the palace.
Yunus Emre..
My Osman Bey...
...and my Orhan told me a lot about you.
We were destined to meet today.
Right...
It is our destiny to see, it
is our destiny to be seen.
Even a herb cannot grow without destiny.
You cannot walk on a way without it.
If you are destined to go somewhere...
...nothing can stop you from going there.
What if we are not sure?
I had a dream, Yunus Emre.
In my dream, I saw bandits on one side...
...and the way of pilgrimage on the other side.
But I am not sure.
Is it better to go...
...or to stay?
Our Allah says: "There is evil in good...
...and there is good in evil.”
You cannot know that before
you set out, Malhun Hatun.
But you are talking about the way of pilgrimage.
The way of pilgrimage is the way of love.
It is the way that goes to Rasulullah (PBUH)
Even if there is a test on that path...
...it is also a blessing.
Allah knows my heart.
Every time I think about the Kaaba,
my feelings defeat my wisdom.
There is such a longing inside me...
Of course, I am willing to take the test.
But what I really think about is...
Am I worthy of putting my face on Beytullah?
What if I'm not?
Do you think that's why horsemen
were chasing me in my dreams?
If Allah calls someone to His presence...
...who can prevent His servant from going there?
As you worry about being worthy enough or not...
...you might be preparing yourself for that way.
You purify your heart from desire and ambition.
You are running away from your...
...nafs and the dirt of the world.
Maybe those bandits...
...were showing this to you.
We don't know.
Now... if you are looking for an answer...
...you will ask it to your heart.
It is your heart that will tell you...
...the meaning of your dream.
I know what my heart says.
When I saw myself in that ihram..
...every way other than
Kaaba is a foreign land for me.
And now...
...I will try hard to be granted with
being worthy enough by my Allah...
...and set out, if Allah permits.
Then..
...may Allah let you go there safely.
Aameen.
Princess Maria.
I heard that you have not been eating anything.
I had different meals prepared
for you. You might like these, huh?
What are you going to do to me, Bala Hatun?
If you send me to Byzantium...
...they will send me to Tajeddin Noyan.
You will lose.
My presence here is dangerous for you.
Will you kill me?
You really think we are barbaric people, huh?
You are our guest, Princess.
The life of our guest...
...is entrusted to us. We will protect you.
You were right, Bala Hatun.
I was not willing to marry Gorklu Khan
They threatened me.
Threatened you?
I love a Turk.
In the Constantine..
I met him when he w£s working as a merchant...
We were going to run away, but....
...we could not.
They took him captive.
They are going to kill him if I don’t marry him.
Only you can help me, please.
Attention! Osman Bey!
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
You can sit down.
I am starting the council meeting with the...
...99 Names of Almighty Allah...
...Who holds us responsible for the war...
...not the victory.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Now we are becoming a state.
Everything will be harder than before.
Mehmet Bey...
Tell me.
What makes the state exist?
Morals.
Morals, right.
Of course, we will protect our morals.
And everyone, everyone will...
...secure justice in their lands.
No one..
...no one will attempt doing
something behind our back.
If justice cannot be secured..
...then the light of that state...
...is about to fade.
Know that.
Everyone understood that
one cannot build a state...
...with gold...
...and Alps.
Osman Bey!
Did you gather the Beys for a council...
...or a ceremony to humiliate us?
Mehmeti
e are not humiliating you, Mehmet Bey!
-We are trying to take you out of the hole...
-Alaeddin...
Beys...
We are mortals.
Sooner or later, we will all pass away.
But... but our dream..
...is longer than a lifetime.
Do not forget that.
Tell me Yakup Bey!
What is our goal?
Our purpose..
..is to spread the name of Allah..
..to the whole World.
That is why..
..no one will try to rise the
banner alone with arrogance.
As..
..this would not fit to any muslim.
Of course..
..everyone will do what is needed.
And we will have the heads of those who does not.
Osman Bey.
We heard what we heard.
And got we got.
However..
..you always told us about state...
...about tradition.
What about army
What about war?
Yakup Bey.
I will speak of them in a council
where you will not be present.
You will go back to your home.
Tajeddin Noyan targets both of us.
Kutahya is in his range.
You will prevent all attacks
that will come from there.
For now..
..for now that is enough.
-Father.
-Mehmed.
If this is appropriate..
..for our act..
..I won't hold back from doing it.
It is appropriate.
Since time has changed..
..then the war will not stay like this.
Of course it will grow.
Everyone, make your preparations.
Come.
-Peace be upon you, my Shahzade.
-Peace be upon you too, Solgur Aga.
Bayindir Bey..
..was going to bring that dog Karacelasun
to palace using secret passages.
-Did they arrive?
-They arrived, my Shahzade.
They will beat that dog mongol until he speaks.
Alright.
First, he will tell what he knows..
..then he will lose his life.
If Allah permits, my Shahzade.
We shouldn’t have come here.
If your aunt finds out..
Orhan took me for a fool, Andra.
He lied to me. He will pay for this.
There he is.
Let's see your answer, Shahzade.
Elcim Hatun.
Osman Bey is waiting for
you at the palace, where to?
Elcim Hatun?
Who is he?
I don't know. Let’s go.
Orhan Bey.
You go.
I will come later.
Are you..
..alright?
I am alright.
Its just that..
..I want to be alone.
Elcim Hatun.
It is hard, what you've been through.
Your father..
..your aunt..
..however, we did not
find their dead now, did we?
With Allah's permission, they're alive.
Elcim Hatun.
Wipe your tears.
There was nothing we could talk about anyways.
Orhan already made his choice it seems.
That mongol dog..
..is in our hands.
We will make him speak. Do not worry.
we will find your father..
..and your aunt.
Holofira?
What is she doing here?
-Brother.
-Sister.
What is it?
Brother, I just saw Holofira.
It seems she saw you both.
She went to the Yenisehir gates, crying.
Holofira..
Who knows what she thought.
Who is Holofira?
Besides, what did she even see?
She is his lover.
And you?
Who are you?
What are you doing with my
brother with these clothes?
I'm from Kayi Tribe and
descendant of Hayme Mother.
I'm Efendize Elcim Hatun.
See you in the palace, Fatma Hatun.
Don't look. Don't look back.
Holofira.
Holofira, it's not as you think!
Get out of my way! I don't want to see you.
Holofira, you're misjudging.
Nothing is as you see!
That's right.
You’re not as you seem at all.
You are just a liar.
Holofira.
You're saying things that you will regret.
Don't.
I can't explain this right now.
But know this.
I have nothing to do with that hatun.
What about the princess?
What about the game you
played for my aunt and me?
You lied to me looking into my eyes!
Although you knew my aunt would turn against you.
You separated us forever.
Nobody can separate us, Lord's daughter.
Just look at me.
Even you can’t get between
you and my love for you.
Look. I didn't lie to you.
It was my duty.
And I did what I needed to do.
Just words.
You only say words, Orhan.
You keep talking about duties.
I'll do you a last favor.
My aunt...
...sent a letter to the emperor.
the Executioner of Roman Empire is coming here.
Who is the Executioner of Roman Empire?
You started a great war, Orhan.
You made my aunt turn against you.
You didn’t put only our love...
..but also your people in dange
You can’t do anything for us anymore.
Take measure for them at least.
the Executioner of Roman Empire...
We're done here, Andra. Let's go.
Who is the Executioner of Roman Empire, Holofira?
Let's go, Andra! Come on;
Brother.
Where is Holofira going?
-Are you alright?
-It's a little complicated, brother.
Are you two affected by the evil eye?
It’s complicated.
But I will figure it out.
We will, brother.
What about you? Tell me.
I won’t let my heart speak anymore.
My only guide will be my mind.
It always shows me the right way.
Let’s go.
Well... I will tell Ulgen Hatun..
...to repel evil eyes from you!
Your duty will be harder.
You won't see your family and child.
You will be with Germiyans.
But I will be sure that they are safe.
Look after them, my Bey.
Osman brought Byzantine to their kneels.
He made all the lords obey him, father.
That hurts me, father.
I should have killed Osman
back then when I had a chance.
-None of these would...
-Shut up!
Mehmed.
Shut up.
We made a mistake.
And we will pay the price in silence.
Shut up.
Osman Bey, Lords sent the taxes you set for them.
Tell the lords..
If there is even one coin missing,
...they will feel my breath on their backs.
I couldn’t see that you were...
...on the right way.
The mistake making..
...a state collapse even
before it's established...
...is the desire of sultanate.
That’s what blinded your eyes, Yakup Bey.
But now I see that you
want to correct your mistake.
That makes you more valuable for me.
I want to give my blessings to
you in this world and in doomsday.
But there is still time.
What time are you talking about, Osman Bey?
The desire of sultanate..
...is like a fire growing
bigger from the ashes again.
Many couldn't keep their promises.
I want to see...
...if you'll have the same desire
when our state grows bigger.
I want to see if you'll stand behind me.
If you do,
...I will give my blessings to
you in this world and in doomsday.
But for now...
...I'm not giving my blessings to you.
Alright, Osman Bey.
Alright.
Have a safe journey.
Take care.
Father.
-Don't do this.
-Shut up, Mehmed.
Get on your horse.
My Bey.
Holofira mentioned someone
to come to the frontiers.
-They call him the Executioner of Rome.
-Oh...
You say...
...things will get more complicated.
You know who he is, my Bey?
No.
But I heard about him.
They call him the Executioner.
He disguises and changes his name all the time.
In fact, he had rebelled against the emperor...
...and made his people get slaughtered.
It seems, he and the emperor made peace.
Now he will attack us.
My Bey, someone who did this to his own people...
...can do much more to his enemies.
Everything will be much harder.
May Allah help us.
Amen.
Let's go.
-Gonca Hatun!
-Ghazi.
Don't go!
-Mother, let me stop her!
Stop this!
Inglorious dastard!
Alps, you go on.
We’ll torture him until he speaks!
He'll tell where Gunduz Bey is before he dies!
Karacelasun or whoever you are.
We don't even know who is holding your leash.
What? Do you serve Tajeddin Noyan now?
What about vengeance?
I will kill you with my hands, Osman.
Whoever gives me this chance,
...I will serve him.
You tortured him well, it seems.
You did.
-Sami!
-My Bey.
-Start cutting him.
-As you order, my Bey.
Well... Leave the tongue.
As you order, my Bey.
He will speak with it.
Come on, man. Come on.
Come on.
Alright. I will tell you.
I will tell you what I know.
Great Olcaytu Khan’s nephew...
...Tajeddin Noyan...
...is coming to Yenisehir.
Let your Bey Osman know this.
Don’t be afraid, Osman's dog.
Alps, keep calm.
Tajeddin Noyan is coming
to this tribe-like city...
...only to talk.
Let him come.
-Inform Osman Bey.
-As you order, Baysungur Alp.
They transferred Elcim's father Gunduz Bey.
Where?
-Where?
-Speak!
To Tajeddin Noyan’s land.
To his headquarters.
It's near Karadere.
Can you go get him?
Will you go to the man who
you are hiding from with fear?
It's over, Osman.
Don’t care about Elcim’s
family but your own family!
Pull back the knife.
My Bey, Tajeddin Noyan is
coming to Yenisehir to talk.
What will you do now, Osman?
Look at me.
I didn’t kill you just because you spoke.
But I know what you did to Gunduz.
Alps.
He should only stand for me to take his head.
Break all the rest of himi
As you order, my Bey.
I don't think Saadet will behave.
Ulgen, keep your eyes wide open.
She must be furious now.
We should be cautious.
Ulgen, where is our guest?
She must be with Fatma. I prepared the meals.
Mother.
Meet Elcim Hatun.
kbasli Gunduz Bey's daughter.
Efendize Elcim Hatun.
Welcome, my daughter.
I am Malhun Hatun.
heard what happened to you. May it pass soon.
Bala Hatun.
We heard that you are from
Hayme mother’s lineage.
Welcome to our family.
Thank you.
When can I talk to Osman Bey?
My father, my aunt, my family...
...are waiting to be saved.
Osman Bey will call you when he has time.
You can have some rest if you want.
You can change your clothes and feel safe.
Ulgen. Let's prepare clothes for Elcim Hatun...
...and make her feel comfortable.
There is no need.
My tribe is entrusted to me...
...until my father sits on his chair.
And until then, I will wear these clothes.
I don't understand. Why?
To keep our people strong, Bala Hatun.
I have to dress like a man..
..until my father comes.
You thought well, Elcim Hatun.
People will feel strong
when they see you like this.
If Allah permits you will come
together with your father and aunt soon.
If Allah permits.
Can I come in?
Come in, Kismet.
Bala Hatun, Osman Bey is
waiting for you at the council.
Thanks to Allah.
She is very smart and brave.
Praise be!
You would not allow me
if I tried to dress like that...
...but you are speaking highly of
another mother's daughter; -Look at you...
My coy daughter is a little jealous these days.
Bala...
What do you think? I guess you did not like her.
Let's get to know her first, time will show us.
Come on, let's go.
I want Germiyan’s all honourable Commanders...
...to come to Kutahya, Kanyumaz.
Before the disaster named Tajeddin Noyan...
...surrounds these lands...
...we will take precautions.
Yes my Sultan.
The real disaster is at the border.
It is not the right time to go to Kutahya.
What are you trying to say, Mehmet?
Osman rebelled against you...
...his Sultan, and declared his sovereign Beylic.
It was not enough, he took
the Princess from llkhanate.
And he got over all the problems.
Now if he defeats Tajeddin Noyan..
...no one will be able to stop Osman.
Mehmeti I see and know...
...everything.
That is why I am going back to Kutahya.
If Osman defeats the disaster
named Tajeddin as well...
...one day, he might become our Sultan.
Do you think I'm too stupid...
...to see this?
Don’t forget. Your sword will be
your mind, and your shield will be...
..Osman's enemies.
We will not solve this issue with blood...
...but with wisdom.
Do you understand me now, Mehmet?
I do, father.
Gonca. Mehmet.
While I am in Kutahya..
...you will manage the frontiers' marketplace.
I will be informed about every step you take.
Yes, father.
Do not do anything without informing me.
My Sultan...
I want to come with you.
I have no one left to go to other than you.
Ulgen left me.
My son turned away from me.
Cerkutay...
You didn’t tell Osman about me...
...they tortured you.
You could speak.
You did not use the mistakes
I made to make me feel small.
My son...
...tried to kill you.
But still, you did not speak.
Thank you Cerkutay.
My door is always open to you.
I will always be the guard
of that door, my Sultan.
I know, I know.
You will be at the frontiers’ marketplace...
...with Mehmet...
...while I am in Kutahya.
You will prevent Mehmet from making a mistake.
As you order, my Sultan.
The executioner of Byzantine on one hand..
..Tajeddin Noyan on the other.
A great war is at our door.
Elcim has told us the situation.
We gathered the union of Turks as well.
For now.
I can not say how the war will be now.
However, it is certain that
it will not look like any other.
The father of Elcim is in
the hands of Tajeddin Noyan.
She told us what happened.
From now on, it is our duty.
May you prosper, Osman Bey.
My father has nearly a thousand
alps that did not get caught.
If you allow me..
..I will call them all to the war.
Alright.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
Take the seal and give it to the clerk.
Sure, my Bey.
The bigger our numbers..
..the better.
Now, Tajeddin Noyan wants to talk to me.
It seems he wants to bargain.
He will want us to bow down,
my Bey. He will want the princess.
More than that, he will want Elcim Hatun.
Are we allowed, my Bey?
Come in.
Tajeddin Noyan is at the gates.
What will we do, Osman Bey?
He won’t get what he hoped for..
..but what I want.
My Shahzade.
Tajeddin Noyan's messenger sends word.
What is it?
They have the captive women..
..and children..
..from Elcim Hatun’s tribe.
If we attack..
..they will kill them with one strike.
What will you do, Alaeddin Bey?
Don’t fall to your anger, son.
Their intention is to drag us into war.
Will he not come to talk?
Let him come. There won't be an attack.
There will be nothing but Osman Bey's bidding.
As you command, my Shahzade.
Tacettin Noyan Headquarters
Obviously, Tacettin Noyan...
..arrived at Yenisehir with his nokers.
The rest is preparing here.
To attack.
However, we will attack them..
..before they do.
-Boran, is it with us?
-My Bey.
It is, my Bey.
Alright.
Come on now, make way to us.
Sıre, my Bey.
Come on.
We didn't think Osman Bey was this young.
Where is Osman?
I am Osman Bey's son, Alaeddin Bey.
It is my duty to welcome you.
Who are you to be equal to me?
You are the nephew of Olcayto..
..the Emir of Emirs..
..Tajeddin Noya
And I am..
..the owner of these lands..
..the pioneer of Turks..
..Alaeddin, son of Osman Bey.
If brother Aktemur was here..
..he would’ve welcomed you instead.
Our rank is equal.
First, tell us why you are here.
I am here because you did not obey
Ulu'l-Emr (superiors) Alaeddin Bey.
You declare your tribe by yourself..
..abduct the bride of llhanids..
..Princess Maria.
You kill Gorklu Khan..
..pray that I haven't destroyed this city.
You are talking about Ulu’l Emr, however..
..do you obey..
..and expect us to do so?
W do not do anything but the orders of Allah.
Shahzade.
We are the sword of Allah on earth.
You will pay for what you did.
I am Tajeddin Noyan.
I will be your calamity.
Come on.
Prisoners' tent.
There, Osman Bey.
Do not worry, we won’t leave
before getting your father.
Come on.
Father?
Welcome, Osman Bey.
I was waiting for you.
Visit turkision.com for more!